<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>The Digital Paper</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/</id><updated>2016-08-06T14:23:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Media.net Interview Experience</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/media-net-interview-experience.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-08-06T14:23:00+05:30</published><updated>2016-08-06T14:23:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chirag Jain</name></author><id>tag:chiragjn.github.io,2016-08-06:/blog/media-net-interview-experience.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;My interview experience at&amp;nbsp;Directi&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Media.net visited my college campus this year for hiring developers for Web/Database Engineer and Application Engineer&amp;nbsp;roles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&amp;#8220;&lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.media.net"&gt;Media.net&lt;/a&gt; a &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://directi.com"&gt;Directi&lt;/a&gt; company, powers the Yahoo! Bing Network Contextual Ads program and is a leading global contextual advertising company that provides a wide range of advertising and traffic monetization solutions.&amp;#8221;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They had four rounds, one programming aptitude and three one-on-one technical interviews. Each round was an elimination round. I have listed down most of the questions asked in all four rounds as best as I can remember them. I am leaving out the solutions to these questions for exercise to the reader.  Some questions are follow up questions. Some of these are open ended questions and can be answered better by self&amp;nbsp;exploration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="round-1-programming-aptitude"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Round 1: Programming&amp;nbsp;Aptitude&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This round has two competitive programming style questions to solve in 90 minutes and was hosted on Codechef. To qualify for Web/Database interview, we had to solve one and for the Application role, both. Even though they had partial scoring scheme, they considered only completely solved&amp;nbsp;solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Question&amp;nbsp;1:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;In a room with N people, some people wear a white band and others wear a black band.
No individual knows the color of their own band.
Each person reports the count of white bands Wi they can see in the room.
Given N such integers return how many are wearing white bands.
If invalid configuration return -1

So example {1,1,2,2} will return 2, {10,10} will return -1, {2,2,2} will return 3

Constraints: 2 ≤ N ≤ 50, 0 ≤ Wi ≤ 50
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Question&amp;nbsp;2:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;You are walking down the escalator to catch a subway train.
The escalator itself moves at a speed of Ve meters per minute.
You can walk down the escalator at a relative speed of Vy meters per minute.
The length of the escalator is L meters.
Trains arrive T minutes apart.
Let t be the time between your arrival to the station if you stand still on the
escalator and the arrival of the last train before your arrival.
Assume that t is a random variable uniformly distributed between 0 and T.
Return the probability of catching an earlier train if you choose to walk down
the escalator instead of standing still on it.

Tc test cases, each has 4 integers Ve, Vy, L, T
0 ≤ Tc ≤ 5 * 10 ^ 7
1 ≤ Ve ≤ 1000
1 ≤ Vy ≤ 1000
1 ≤ L ≤ 10 ^ 5
1 ≤ T ≤ 10 ^ 6

Input:

2
10
10
20
2
10
10
100
4

Output:

0.5
1.0
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I managed to solve the first one quickly. It just happened that I had solved the second problem before in their off-campus internship round and got it accepted back then, but despite submitting the same logic this time I got a wrong answer verdict. Nobody managed to solve it this time. I tried contacting the on-campus co-ordinators, they agreed that they did reuse the problem but they said they tested everything. I wasn&amp;#8217;t satisfied. As software engineers shouldn&amp;#8217;t we expect the code we wrote yesterday to work the same today&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the test, 12 from our college were selected to appear for the Web/Database interview rounds the next day in Directiplex(Mumbai&amp;nbsp;office).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="round-2-technical-interview-algorithms-ds"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Round 2: Technical Interview (Algorithms, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DS&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I raised my aptitude issue, interviewer said he will inform the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HR&lt;/span&gt; about it. Since I mentioned some web projects on resume, my interview started with web questions. All questions marked with double asterisks needed to be coded on&amp;nbsp;paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell me about different &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HTTP&lt;/span&gt; response codes&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How is a website loaded&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do sessions work in &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PHP&lt;/span&gt; ? Where is session stored ? How do stateless http requests match the same session for a user&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why did you choose Laravel only for &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PHP&lt;/span&gt;? Why not some other&amp;nbsp;framework?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you know about &lt;span class="caps"&gt;XSS&lt;/span&gt; attacks&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;** Get second highest number from array in single&amp;nbsp;pass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;** Get second last node in linked list without knowing the&amp;nbsp;length.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;** Print all perfect cubes between L and&amp;nbsp;R.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;** From an array, find the minimum length subarray which sums upto strictly greater than a given number&amp;nbsp;x.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What databases have you worked with ? Have you heard of in memory databases ? Advantages and disadvantages over disk based database&amp;nbsp;systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What mechanisms do you think you will need to have to be able to use in memory database&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This round was easy and I was able to give satisfactory answers. 11 of us were selected for the next&amp;nbsp;round.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="round-3-technical-interview-web-databases"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Round 3: Technical Interview (Web,&amp;nbsp;Databases)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This round was very profile specific and I barely managed to produce satisfactory answers but I kept giving answers even though I was uncertain about a lot of&amp;nbsp;things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What all things to take care of while calling third party APIs ? (you don&amp;#8217;t own the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;API&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does session work ? Where is it stored ? Alternatives to store ? What if I disabled cookies on client side, how will server recognise my session now ? Any way to fallback on something else ? How do sessions propagate accross requests&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;XML&lt;/span&gt;/ &lt;span class="caps"&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt; parsing in Javascript, given some example , write code to get some value from &lt;span class="caps"&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt; object or &lt;span class="caps"&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt; array out, optimise the written&amp;nbsp;code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How does Ajax work&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are cookies ? What would you store in them ? Where are cookies stored ? What is that path on the disk ? As an end user, if I don&amp;#8217;t know the disk path, is there someway I can view the cookies&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is XMLHTTPRequest&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Storage engines in MySQL ? Differences between InnoDB and MyISAM ? What other storage engines you have heard of&amp;nbsp;?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You get results from 3rd party &lt;span class="caps"&gt;API&lt;/span&gt; in paginated fashion or say you scrape the pages, how would you get the total count of results without parsing all pages ? (&lt;em&gt;I asked if the pagination was even, interviewer denied and I got stuck for long time, gave some approaches but nothing seemed a complete solution&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write an &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SQL&lt;/span&gt; query to get Average Salary per department, with department name for the following schema: &lt;span class="caps"&gt;EMP&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class="caps"&gt;ID&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="caps"&gt;NAME&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="caps"&gt;SAL&lt;/span&gt;,D_ID), &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DEPT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class="caps"&gt;ID&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="caps"&gt;NAME&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This round was difficult for me. 10 of us were selected for the final round held on the next&amp;nbsp;day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="round-4-technical-interview-algorithms-ds-cs-fundamentals"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Round 4: Technical Interview (Algorithms, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DS&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CS&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Fundamentals)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I raised my aptitude issue again with the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HR&lt;/span&gt;, but I got no immediate response. My interview turn came the last among all&amp;nbsp;candidates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;dl class="first docutils"&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Given a blackbox(no details of internal implemenation) class Queue{ void enqueue(int); int dequeue();}, make only two instances and implement stack using&amp;nbsp;them.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;em&gt;I initially assumed there is a size() function, but interviewer denied my first draft, then I managed to write it using just the given two&amp;nbsp;functions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;dl class="first docutils"&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;Given a 2d array of &amp;#8216;x&amp;#8217;s and &amp;#8216;o&amp;#8217;s, where &amp;#8216;x&amp;#8217; is land and &amp;#8216;o&amp;#8217; is water, return number of continents, land is connected 4 ways not&amp;nbsp;diagonally.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wrote a floodfill algorithm with extra visited[][] array but interviewer told me to do it without the visited[][] array. I converted &amp;#8216;x&amp;#8217;s to &amp;#8216;o&amp;#8217;s in my original input array but again interviewer told me 2d array is read only. At this point I was stuck for a long time. Later interviewer gives me a hint that continents would always be rectangles. I got the hint, it made coding tedious, I started coding, but after 5 mins of code scribbling, interviewer decided to move&amp;nbsp;on.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;dl class="first docutils"&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;10 million strings each of length 10 consisting A-Z,a-z,0-9, design an efficient hashing algorithm with no/minimal&amp;nbsp;collisions.&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;&lt;em&gt;Again stuck for a long time, After 2-3 approaches, interviewer was not satisfied and decided to end the&amp;nbsp;interview.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again this round was difficult for me but here is the twist!
Directi considered my issue and gave me a fair shot at Application profile. I was interviewed for Application profile and I didn&amp;#8217;t knew it till the end. At the end of the interview, my interviewer told me I was interviewed for Application profile instead of Web/Database and I didn&amp;#8217;t make the Application profile bar. I was offered the Web Developer&amp;nbsp;role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="conclusion-and-advice"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion and&amp;nbsp;Advice&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To conclude, it was a positive experience for me and 8 out of 12 including me were hired for the Web developer role. Rejection is not always a bad thing! After getting rejected from Morgan Stanley interview few days back I was able to target and prepare better. And there are off-campus rounds every year to apply&amp;nbsp;in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol class="arabic simple" start="0"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Algorithms and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DS&lt;/span&gt;, read the classical problems and paradigms. Learn &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.geeksforgeeks.org/fundamentals-of-algorithms/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.geeksforgeeks.org/data-structures/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Operating Systems, Databases and Computer Networks questions are often&amp;nbsp;asked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice competitive programming contests on &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://codeforces.com"&gt;Codeforces&lt;/a&gt;, especially as virtual contests to get the feel of time bound tests. Don&amp;#8217;t just skip to editorial very early, think, think very hard!. Don&amp;#8217;t just read/copy algorithms, understand and implement them, you will code the same thing very confidently and quickly the next&amp;nbsp;time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get used to writing code on paper. Typing is very&amp;nbsp;easy!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get ready to answer anything related to the profile you have applied for. Take your time and think out loud even if&amp;nbsp;unsure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never assume anything! Ask. We live in a world where tools &amp;#8216;just&amp;#8217; work out of the box. Directi has very tech savvy people, there is literally tech scribbled all over their glass panes and whiteboards. It is very important to not take things for granted and know the internals/working of the&amp;nbsp;tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research the company and their&amp;nbsp;work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluate yourself, know your strengths and weaknesses, how to describe&amp;nbsp;yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also if you end up in a issue like mine, don&amp;#8217;t hesitate to talk with the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HR&lt;/span&gt; as soon as possible, but do so with proof in&amp;nbsp;hand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="best-of-luck"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Best of&amp;nbsp;luck!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;P.S.&lt;/span&gt; I have a comments section now. You can leave any questions / suggestions / corrections / feedback&amp;nbsp;below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="Technology"></category><category term="interview"></category><category term="programming"></category><category term="competitive-programming"></category><category term="problem-solving"></category></entry><entry><title>ProFit app showcase</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/profit-app-showcase.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-02-29T22:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2016-02-29T22:05:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chirag Jain</name></author><id>tag:chiragjn.github.io,2016-02-29:/blog/profit-app-showcase.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;The ProFit android app&amp;nbsp;showcase&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So a lot of people asked me about what my team made that won us the first prize at SportsHack 2016 Hackathon held by &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://india.zonestartups.com/"&gt;Zone Startups&lt;/a&gt;,India in Association with &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.ausport.gov.au/ais"&gt;Australia Institute of Sports&lt;/a&gt;.So here&amp;#8217;s to ProFit - The PROfessional FITness&amp;nbsp;App.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="ProFit App Icon" class="align-center" src="images/profit/ic_launcher.png" style="width: 144.0px; height: 144.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="about-profit"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;About&amp;nbsp;ProFit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ProFit is a fitness platform that provides features such as deep Google Now integration, which allows the user to log any activity to ProFit without having to open the app using his/her voice, ProFit aims at minimizing tedious interactions such as data entry by automating it as much as possible. To do the same, ProFit also allows users to create sessions(set of activities) which can be logged together and use data provided by Google&amp;nbsp;Fit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A major part of ProFit lies in Gamification, ProFit has its own Fitness currency called ‘Fitons’, Users are granted Fitons based on the activities they perform and other personal parameters. Users can earn bragging rights by sharing graphs, ratings and activities on social media to compare  with their peers. ProFit also provides dynamic suggestions to the user based on their history, their goals and safety&amp;nbsp;criteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ProFit also lets you set said Goals which your suggestions are based on, such as ‘5k Marathon’. ProFit also shows comprehensive statistics about your activities and goals. ProFit provides a backend admin to monitor and update all users’ data and provide&amp;nbsp;suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="screenshots"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Screenshots&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="text-align-center docutils container"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen" src="images/profit/home0.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen" src="images/profit/home2.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen FAB Menu" src="images/profit/homefab.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen Sugeestion Expanded" src="images/profit/homeexpanded.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Logging Activity" src="images/profit/activity.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Adding Sessions" src="images/profit/sessions.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Use your voice with Google Now to Log Sessions/Activities/Weight" src="images/profit/gnow.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="And Google Now and we will do the Magic" src="images/profit/gnowreact.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Beautiful statistics graphs" src="images/profit/stats1.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Beautiful statistics graphs" src="images/profit/stats2.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Beautiful statistics graphs" src="images/profit/stats3.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Share your graphs on Twitter" src="images/profit/twittershare.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Set some goals" src="images/profit/goals.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Profile Screen" src="images/profit/profile.png" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="screencast-clips"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Screencast&amp;nbsp;clips&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="text-align-center docutils container"&gt;
&lt;img alt="All the tabs" src="images/profit/tabs_scr.gif" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen DecoView Animation" src="images/profit/homedeco.gif" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Floating Action Button To Toolbar Animation" src="images/profit/fab.gif" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Home Screen Expanding ListView Suggestions" src="images/profit/homeexpand.gif" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;img alt="Profile Screen DecoViews" src="images/profit/profile.gif" style="width: 216.0px; height: 384.0px;" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="the-fitons-team"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Fitons&amp;nbsp;team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;img alt="Profile Screen DecoViews" class="align-center" src="images/profit/fitons.jpeg" /&gt;
&lt;div style="font-size:0.95rem;text-align:center;"&gt;From left to right: Chirag Jain, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/s4shyam95"&gt;Shyam Mehta&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/paren200"&gt;Paren Desai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="for-the-geeks"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;For the&amp;nbsp;Geeks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The source code for this Android app is available &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/chiragjn/ProFit-Android"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.But it is no where near production level code and it contains deliberate &amp;#8216;hacks&amp;#8217; to make things work.Also we used Apache &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ANT&lt;/span&gt; build system(will never again,we hit the 65K dex methods limit :P ) instead of Gradle so checkout project.properties files for all the awesome libraries we&amp;nbsp;used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, will update this article with the minor problems we faced during&amp;nbsp;development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="credits"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Credits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.facebook.com/s4shyam95"&gt;Shyam Mehta&lt;/a&gt; for the summary on&amp;nbsp;ProFit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vitaly Rubstov for his inspiring &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://works.yalantis.com/workout-book/"&gt;Workout Book &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UI&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;UX&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;concept&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="Technology"></category><category term="technology"></category><category term="software"></category><category term="fitness"></category><category term="hackathon"></category><category term="android"></category><category term="fitons"></category></entry><entry><title>The Coming Soon Plugin for Pelican</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/the-coming-soon-plugin-for-pelican.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-12-04T23:51:00+05:30</published><updated>2015-12-04T23:51:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chirag Jain</name></author><id>tag:chiragjn.github.io,2015-12-04:/blog/the-coming-soon-plugin-for-pelican.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Make drafts visible as &amp;#8220;Coming&amp;nbsp;Soon&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Want to keep your pelican blog readers excited with what you are working with?
I made a small plugin for Pelican which allows you to add &amp;#8220;Coming Soon&amp;#8221; Status to your blog posts.Your readers will see these articles listed on your blog but not its&amp;nbsp;content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plugin is open source and available on &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/chiragjn/pelican-coming-soon-plugin"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; . Please see the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;README&lt;/span&gt;.md on on Github on how to integrate and use this&amp;nbsp;plugin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img alt="Screenshot" class="align-center" src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/chiragjn/pelican-coming-soon-plugin/master/screenshot.png" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;P.S.&lt;/span&gt; This plugin can make you lazy!
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;P.S.S.&lt;/span&gt; This plugin is not completely tested and runs a delete over output drafts to remove them from&amp;nbsp;published&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="technology"></category><category term="software"></category><category term="pelican"></category></entry><entry><title>Coming Soon Pelican Plugin Demo</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/drafts/coming-soon-pelican-plugin-demo.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-12-04T04:08:00+05:30</published><updated>2015-12-04T04:08:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chirag Jain</name></author><id>tag:chiragjn.github.io,2015-12-04:/blog/drafts/coming-soon-pelican-plugin-demo.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;A demo article for Coming Soon pelican&amp;nbsp;plugin&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">This article will be published soon</content><category term="Technology"></category><category term="software"></category><category term="pelican"></category></entry><entry><title>I use…</title><link href="https://chiragjn.github.io/blog/i-use.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-12-04T00:32:00+05:30</published><updated>2015-12-04T00:32:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Chirag Jain</name></author><id>tag:chiragjn.github.io,2015-12-04:/blog/i-use.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;What I develop&amp;nbsp;on/using&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="hardware"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hardware&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="dell-inspiron-15r-n5010"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Dell Inspiron 15R&amp;nbsp;N5010&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class="literal-block"&gt;
CPU : 2.4GHz Intel™ 1st Generation Core i3 370M
Memory : 1.3GHz 4GB DDR3 RAM
Disk : 320GB HDD + 1TB WD HDD
Graphics : 64MB dedicated Intel HD Graphics
Operating System : OSX ElCaptian 10.11.2,OSX Yosemite 10.10.1, Windows 10
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="yu-yureka"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;YU&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Yureka&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre class="literal-block"&gt;
Codename : tomato
CPU : Qualcomm® Snapdragon™ 615 - 4x 1.7GHz Cortex-A53 + 4x 1.0GHz Cortex-A53
Memory : 2GB LPDDR3 800 MHz Single-channel 32-bit
Disk : 16GB eMMC
Graphics : Adreno 405
Operating System : Android™ Marshmallow
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="other-mobile-devices"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Other Mobile&amp;nbsp;Devices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xolo &lt;span class="caps"&gt;Q700S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xiaomi Redmi&amp;nbsp;1s&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sony Ericsson&amp;nbsp;Cedar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nokia&amp;nbsp;2690&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="software"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="text-editors"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;1. Text&amp;nbsp;Editors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sublime Text&amp;nbsp;2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;GNU&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Nano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="ides"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2.&amp;nbsp;IDEs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android&amp;nbsp;Studio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xcode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PyCharm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PhpStorm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="blog-engine"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;3. Blog&amp;nbsp;Engine&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pelican hosted with Github&amp;nbsp;Pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="blog-theme"&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;4. Blog&amp;nbsp;Theme&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class="simple"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/chiragjn/The-Digital-Paper-src/tree/master/themes/perec-mod"&gt;Perec-Mod&lt;/a&gt; - A modified version of &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/ggimse/perec"&gt;Perec&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="General"></category><category term="hardware"></category><category term="software"></category></entry></feed>